

## Phattanothai Pukham

# Software Developer

## **Personal Information**

Nick Name	Fluke
Military Status	Reservist
Date of Availaility	Immediately

I don't have much work experience. But I am ready to learn and develop. I'm the type of person who likes a challenge. easy to get along with I like to try new things and develop myself all the time.

I hope that we will have the opportunity to work together.

#### **Contect**

Tel	0635957755
Email	phattanothai.pukham@gmail.com
Address	96 Moo.6 Tambon
	Thanthong, Amphur Phan,
	Chiang Rai 57250
Github	https://github.com/phattanotai
Website	https://portfolios.gracia.tech

#### Skills

Graphic	Design		
Fair			
UX/UI D	esign		
Fair			
Coding			
	Fluent		
<b>Databa</b> s	e		
	Good		
Server			
	Standard		
Researc	h		
	Excelle	nt	

## **EDUCATION**

2012-2016 Bachelor of Science Program in Computer Science

Suan Sunandha Rajabhat University

GPA 3.21

2009-2016 Pali language

Wat Paknam Bhasicharoen

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Jan. 2022 - Present Freelance Part-Time Software Developer

(Web App, Mobile App, REST API)

1 Nov. 2020 - Jan. 2022 Full Stack Developer Full-Time (Web App,

Mobile App, REST API) at OTEN INNOVATION, (Remote Work)

1 Sep. 2020 - 1 Nov. 2020 Freelance Software Developer (Web App,

REST API, LINE Bot) at Chiang Rai

1 Jun. 2019 - 31 Aug. 2020 Programmer Full-Time (Web App, Mobile App,

tcp server, REST API) at World Gps Tracker

Co.,Ltd, Chiang Rai

http://wgtgps.net/login

1 May 2017 – 30 Apr. 2019 Fort Mengraimaharaj Hospital, Chiang Rai

#### **ABILITIES**

Coding Nodejs, Javascript, Typescript, PHP, SQL, Python

Flask, Expressjs, Slim, Nestjs

Angular, Vuejs, React, Nextjs, React Native, Ionic, Jquery Bootstrap, Material Design, Tailwind CSS, Ant Design

DevExtreme, Rxjs, Redux, Vuex

One Signal, Pusher, Selenium, Graphql, Apollo, Threejs

Sequelize, TypeORM, Mongoose

Google Map, Leaflet Map, Longdo Map

Polling, Server Sent Event, Websocket, SocketIO

Integrate Api e.g. dlt, scg, cpf, Integrate gamebrand e.g.

sexy, pg, sbobet send sms email, line api

Database Postgresql, Mysql, Sql Server, Mongodb, Redis, SQLite

Config Replication Master and Slave Server
Postgis, Geo, Stored Procedure, Database trigger

Server Ubuntu, Window Server, Nginx, Load Balance, Cluster Mode,

Kubernetes, Docker, Docker Swarm, Kong Api Gateway, GCP,

AWS

Tools Gitlab, Bitbucket, Github, Jira, Asana, Gather Town, Slack,

CircleCI, GitlabCI, Netlify, Cloudflare, Prometheus, Grafana,

gRPC, RabbitMQ

Research Microfrontend, Service Mesh Isito, ArgoCD, Jenkins, Apache

Kafka, Terraform, Ansible, SonarQube

Elasticsearch, Opensearch, LevelDB, Firebase

Flutter, Laravel, Spring Boot, .Net Core, FastAPI, Rust, Golang, Solidity, Wab3, Ethers.js, Kotlin, Swift, Unity,

Facebook API, WebRTC, WASM